One day, in one city
立正！
Attent-ion!
向右转！
Squad move to the right. Right TURN
向前开步走！
Squad by the Right. Quick March
师兄， 你这么胖也敢来？
How come a fat bloke like you is admitted to the cadet school?
看那边
Look there
你看你， 骨瘦如柴， 没前途的
Look at you. No hope for skinny
多吃点东西吧
Eat more
如今妞儿喜欢胖子吗？
Now the gals like chubby blokes?
肯定是！
Definitely!
帽子掉了
Your hat falls off
看来， 我也要多吃点东西
I should eat plenty of food
是的
That's it
出来了， 出来了
They're coming
出来了        我看看...
Coming... Let me take a look...
出来了， 那边...
They're coming. There...
好帅呀， 你看他胸前那撮毛
He's so handsome Look at his breast hair
他跟我打招呼呀！
He's greeted me!
别搞我呀！
Don't touch me!
你看， 我的Fans又来看我了
Look! My fans are there
简直是猪排
They're hags
不， 我觉得她们好正点
I don't think so In fact, they're copies of Kylie Minogue
真有品味
Good taste
停
Halt
有！
Yes, sir!
叶长官要见你
Officer Ye called you
24138， 早上饭堂用餐 你坐我旁边
You sat next to me this morning, 24138
记不记得我吃过什么？
Do you remember what I had for the breakfast?
很清楚， 长官
Yes, sir
你吃了一只全乳猪 、 一笼寿包
You had buns, a roasted suckle pig
一只炸子鸡和一条东星
Fried chicken and steamed leopard
吃早餐像过头七 看来你命不长矣， 长官
Such a big meal can cause heart disease Be cautious
岂有此理， 先欠着
I'll pay later
还有， 饭堂文叔叫我提醒你
And the canteen staff told me to remind you...
方便的话请你清了欠单， 长官
to foot the bill if convenient, sir
你少说一句行不行？
Can you stop talking about this?
24138， 你觉得我为人怎样？
What do you think about me, 24138?
不清楚， 长官
I have no idea, sir
不过你绰号 “煎酿三宝”
But your nickname's Tri-ble
缩骨 、 卸责 、 老... 土
That is uncharitable irresponsible and unfashionable
所以大概也猜到点， 长官
So I get some clues, sir
知不知道我今天穿了鸳鸯袜？
Do you know I've worn two different socks?
完全不起眼， 长官
No, sir. It's difficult to notice
因为你本身高低肩 、 长短手 、 大小眼
'cos you have arms and eyes of different sizes
坐得东倒西歪
and sit like a dog
那对鸳鸯袜跟你配得天衣无缝
All these matches you and your socks
所以并不起眼， 长官
So it's difficult to notice the different socks, sir
这么坦白干嘛？
Is it necessary to be so honest?
没大没小
Remember: You're just a cadet
得罪我俩， 你可就没事做了
If you don't respect us your career will be finished
那正好， 我最怕有任务
That's fine I don't want any assignments
尤其是卧底之类最不适合我， 长官
like being an undercover, sir
你怎知道我们要派你做卧底？
How do you know we'll assign you as undercover?
他俩见过你们后， 哭得死去活来
They cry like dying patients after seeing you
不是要做卧底吗？
It must be this assignment that made them cry, right?
错， 做卧底是无尚光荣
Nope. It's honorable to be an undercover
只有警队精英才做得到
Only those elites will be picked to be the undercover
我现派你们混进黑社会搜集情报
I send you three to infiltrate the gangs to spy on their movements
你们就当作被警校开除， 马上走
You'd be kicked out by the cadet school Go now
以后只向我和叶长官报告
You only report to Mr. Ye and me
对吧， 傻强
I'm right, Crazy Tom
我们要赖死不去， 他才派我们去
He only assigned the job to us if we're reluctant to accept it
真有你的， 仁哥
You have your own way, Ray
如果我们不去做卧底 哪有时间泡妞？
If we aren't undercover how can we have time to date gals?
我已约了三个美女 买好雪糕在门口等我们
I've dated three beauties They've bought ice-cream for us
在哪？        在哪？
Where're they? Where're they?
看
Look
到警校来， 就得守警校的规矩
You gotta follow the regulations of the cadet school
不守规矩的就跟他们一样
Like them, those who fail to do so
“给开除”
will be kicked out of the school
你们谁想跟他交换？
Who want to switch places with them?
我想跟他交换， 长官！
Me, sir!
我也想！
Me too!
长官， 我也想跟他们换
Me too, sir!
不行， 长官， 我想跟他们换
I really want to be them, sir!
仁哥， 清早六点叫我来拜什么？
Why do you wake us up so early, Ray?
别乱说话， 我们现在是黑社会恶棍
Don't bullshit. We're gangsters
黑社会当然要拜关公
So we got to pray the God of Kuan for blessing
你们这些混蛋！
You three bastards!
警察拜关公， 黑社会也拜关公
The police prays the God of Kuan so do you gangster
关公帮得了谁？
Who should He bless?
大婶， 你是谁？
Who're you, nanny?
我是关公的后人
I'm God of Kuan's descendant
到底是谁？
What's your name?
关芝琳！
Rosamund Kuan!
你是关芝琳？
You're Rosamund?
他不就是黄家诺？
Then he must be Jimmy?
Jimmy!...
Jimmy!
关芝琳， 关芝琳... 这里是庙
Here's temple, Rosamund...
仁哥， 你要我们入黑社会
Ray, we're gangsters
但又不能干黑社会的事 那该怎么搞？
But we can't commit crime What should we do?
我们干些凶狠点的事
Then we maybe do something violent
例如？
Like what?
例如打劫
Robbery
敢不敢？
Dare you?
看什么？再看连你的奶也喝！
What're you looking at? Suck your breast milk!
王八蛋！
Bastard!
胖子， 你先砸
You go first, Chubbie
干嘛我先砸？
Why should I go first?
你砸...         你砸...
Your turn Your turn...
那我先打！砸烂你...
I first! Break it...
别打...
Don't...
谁叫你们来捣乱？
Who told you to play tyrant here?
胖子！
Chubbie!
告诉你大哥
Tell your big brother
我们是专在九龙捣蛋的恶棍！
The boundary of our gang is in Westminster!
大哥， 有人找你        找我？
Bro, someone calls you Me?
我是他大哥， 大他两岁
I'm his brother two years older than him
不是这种大哥， 老伯
Not brother, uncle
是真的黑社会的大哥呀
It's the Big Brother
我儿子个个都是黑社会大哥
All of my sons are Big Brothers of different gangs
吹牛！        我不信！
Bullshit! I don't believe this!
你看
Look
胖子， 黑社会呀
Gangsters, Chubbie
好！
Great!
砸你的店
Spoil your shop
凶一点， 再凶一点
More fierce
砸你的店！
Spoil your shop!
你看到了， 他多凶狠
Look. He's very fierce
大哥， 我们很想入黑社会
Bro, we wanna join your gangs
你收我们做打手吧
Please hire us as gangsters
我爸做的纸扎人， 今晚打斋用的
The paper figures are for tonight's funeral
都给你们砸烂了， 你们赔得起吗？
You wrecked them all Can you afford them?
赔不起
Nope
那该怎办？
What should you do?
胖子， 到底还要站多久？
Chubbie, how long should we stand?
起码要等到化宝
Till the paper figures are burnt
等不是问题， 胖子
It's no big deal, Chubbie
要有人相信才行呀
But nobody burns the paper figures
我来化宝
It's time to burn the paper figures
不怕， 我还有火机
Never mind. I have a lighter
你干嘛打他？你是纸扎人呀
Why do you beat him? You're a paper figure
他要烧我， 我当然还手嘛
He wanted to burn me I had to fight back
要是给人发现...
What if people found we...
妈妈...         什么事？
Mum... What's the matter?
纸扎人打我呀
The paper figures beat me
你个混蛋！还顾着玩？
You naughty boy! Still play in the memorial service?
老爸死了， 你不伤心吗？
Your dad's died. Aren't you sad?
多事！
Mind your business!
敢报信...
You grass...
够了， 走吧
That's enough. Go
走吧， 胖子， 别拿人家的祭品
Go. Don't take people's oblations
走...
Run...
长官， 我顶不住了！
I can't stand the life like this, sir!
警察追我们， 黑社会也追我们
Both the police and the gangsters fight us
顶？怎么顶？你来顶吧
Hold on? How can we make it? You have a try
又是你们三个？
You three again?
你们三个真堕落...
You three are going to dogs...
我不跟你们做朋友！
I won't make friends with you!
狗东西！
Dogs!
狗屁！
Doghouse!
狗屎！
Dog-shit!
36D呀
36D!
我劲姐都不认识， 你瞎了眼？
You don't know who I'm? It's Cool Lady
给我记住这三个
Remember these three blokes
他们是贱货中的贱货， 人渣中的人渣
They're the worst dogs
就算我们一辈子找不到男人
Even you don't find your Mr. Right
也千万别要这些垃圾！明白吗？
Don't give them a chance! Get it?
明白！
Yes, madam!
我们明明是好人来的
We're good blokes
刚才见到那些师姐...
But those policewomen...
她们瞧不起咱们， 还说我们是人渣
Looked down upon us She even said we're the worst dogs
胖子， 别这样， 北姑正看着
Chubbie, don't be like this The whores are looking at us
我们讲英语
Let's speak English
北姑， 不会英语的
North-girls, don't know English
好主意
He's damn right
当然
Of course
我不明白， 我想做个好人
I don't know. I want to be a good man
想泡泡师姐...
I want to date those policewomen
可她当我是垃圾
But, she look me down
还说我是人渣...
and call me Mr. Jar
你应该说:我非常失望
You'd have said, I'm very disappointed with those policewomen
她们误会我
Misunderstanding me
我不是垃圾 、 人渣
But actually I'm not the way they think I'm
我定会成为一个好汉
and I want to be a very good man
你们应该多说一点英语吧
You should practise your English
中国已加入世贸啦
China's joined the WTO
若你需要私人补习， 可以找我
Hey, if you want private lessons just call me
卖淫只是我的兼职
You know prostitution is just my part-time job
卖淫？
Prostitution?
兼职？
Part-time job?
你看他走路的样子， 在装帅
Look at the way he walks. Jack the Lad
三个月了
It's another three months
三个月又三个月...
Three months after three months...
一年都快过了， 老板
It's already a year, boss
你不还球赛赌债也先还赌马欠的债呀
You'd better foot at least one bill
我们先别提那笔账
Forget about the bills first
你说过， 三个月又三个月
You've said it's another three months
可我每三个月降一次
I've been downgraded every three months
降到现在 我快从穿西装变成穿军装了
I'll be police constable soon
你们还没人进入黑社会 叫我如何交代？
But you haven't infiltrated the gangs How can I report to the senior?
回归后， 香港警员比警犬还凶
After 1997, the Police is much fiercer than the Alsatians
哪还有黑社会？
Any gangsters left?
不会吧？
Really?
龙虾的头马曾琛开了间车房
Sam, Loster's second-in-command runs a garage
你们进得了那车房就进得了黑社会
Once you work in the garage you infiltrate the gang
别耍啦
Don't fool me
龙虾的头马不是四大天王吗？
The second-in-command of Lobster's gang are Four Kings, right?
这不用你管
Mind your own business
只要拿到曾琛的犯罪证据给我 你们可以退休
Once you collect evidence of Sam's criminal activities. You may be free
你讲了九千多次啦！
You've already said this a thousand times!
你们三个对我态度要好一点
You three must respect me
现在整个警署只有我知道你们是卧底
Only I know you're undercover
如果我删除了档案
If I delete your files
你们就一辈子做黑社会了
you'll be gangsters forever
不， 是你对我们三个态度要好一点
I think you must respect us
现在全港的黑社会没人知道你被降职
No gangsters in Hong Kong know you're downgraded
要是我们说出去， 你就完蛋了
If we tell them, you'll be finished
别说这些了， 我带了些东西给你们
Forget about these I've brought you some gifts
一人一个
One per head
劳力士？
Ro-les?
怎么是手表， 不是奖金吗？
Why isn't it bonus?
二十五块的地摊货， 合你们做卧底用
Twenty-five dollars each They match the undercover
长官， 你当了几十年警察
You've joined the Police over ten years, sir
真劳力士都没有一只？
How come you don't even have a real Ro-les watch?
这是真的劳力士， 你看！拿去戴吧
This is a real Ro-les watch Look! Wear this
还有， 下次约会卧底
And next time
别老装酷上天台
don't meet us on the roof like the film characters
人家以为我们是来搞清洁的 王八！
People will think we're doing the cleaning, idiot!
刮风下雨来这里， 害我们变落汤鸡 王八！
If it's raining we'll be wet, idiot!
被误会我们来偷女人底裤更糟 大王八！
People may think we come for ladies' underwear, idiot!
你们三个王八说完没有？
Have you finished?
说完我走了
If so, I go
到哪去？
Where do you go?
你去哪里？
Where are you going?
去送叶长官最后一程
To the memorial service of Officer Ye
他死了吗？
He'd died?
比死更惨
Much poorer than death
他现正前往 『无间地狱』
He's going to the Endless Graveyard
从今天起， 他要忍受永无间断的痛苦
From now onward he has to bear the endless pains
永远受监视， 不能泡妞
He's watched. He can't date gals
永远有得看没得上
He can see but can't go
叶长官， 你安心去吧
Officer Ye, may you be blissful
他就是早上抓回来的色魔？
This is the sexual offender caught this morning?
律师没来之前， 他什么都不会说的
He doesn't say anything unless the lawyer's come
好像还有个同党跟他一起非礼人 是呀
It seems that he has a co-worker Yeah
一个扣， 一个摸
One put a hand round the neck And one lays a hand on the victims
我知道
Get it
但我怕套不到口供， 抓不到他的同党
If he doesn't say anything we can't catch his co-worker
那怎么办？
What should we do?
律师没来， 我是不会说话的
I don't say anything before the lawyer comes
我是刘律师， 有没有打电话回家？
I'm Mr. Lau, a lawyer Have you called your family?
律师， 你真可爱
You're cute, lawyer
不用东张西望
No need to look around this room
有律师在场， 他们不敢录影
The camera doesn't record once here's a lawyer
录了也没用
Even it records you, it's no use
他好帅呀
You're handsome
要不要打电话通知家人？
Do you want to call your family?
你好年轻呀
You look so young
他们好像知道你兄弟的住处
It seems that they know where your co-worker's in
他恐怕跑不掉了
I think he can't escape
你挺帅的
You're quite handsome
你们不是一个扣一个摸吗？
One put a hand round the neck And one lays a hand on the victims, right?
我就是摸的那个！
I just lay the hand on the ball!
他的脸怎么变青了？
Why does his face turn grey?
我手势怎么样？
How's my technique?
轻一点...
Lighter, please
想套我？没那么容易
Spy on me? No way
要不要打电话给你家人？
Do you want to call your family?
不用... 帮我叫救护车， 拜托
No... call ambulance, please
我进去        会不会搞砸的？
I gotta help him! Will you spoil his plan?
不管这么多了！
But I can't leave him alone!
你越看越帅
You look really handsome
混蛋！搞我男朋友？ 我跟你拼！搞我男朋友？
Wanna smooch my man? I'll kill you!
师姐， 你好凶狠呀
You're so fierce, madam
不好意思
Excuse me
这样呢？
How about this?
更恐怖呀！
More terrible!
其实， 任何美女在我面前我都没感觉
I don't have any feeling on any beauties
当年琛哥派我去做卧底
Sam sent me to be the undercover
我肯去， 并不是因为他
I agreed not for him
而是为了一个人
But for another person
当然不是他， 过一点
It surly isn't him. Farther
再过一点
Farther
没错， 就是她
Yes, it's her
她就是大哥的女人， Mandy
This is Big Bro's woman, Mandy
我一生中的最爱
The only woman I love
师傅说我这条命是...
The fortune-teller said...
一仗功成万骨枯
I'll hit the jackpot
一百块可以召四个北姑
with the help ofjackass
你们这帮人跟着我不少日子了
You've worked for me for a period of time
要在你们当中挑一个去做卧底
I'll choose one of you to be the undercover
的确不容易
It isn't a piece of cake
不过现在已经选好了
but I've made the decision
华弟， 就你吧
Watson, it's you
多谢琛哥！
Thanks Sam!
够了... 倒杯茶来...
OK... make us the tea...
快， 倒杯茶来...
Hurry up
给兄弟们脸子
Give face to the co-workers
喝过这杯茶， 祝你在警察部一帆风顺
May you be prosperous in the Police
大家干杯！...
Cheers!
不知琛哥和Mandy 现在怎么样呢？
What's going on with Sam and Mandy?
琛哥怎么混的？整天傻乎乎
What's wrong with Sam? He's fey
不开架步 、 不卖盗版 、 不卖毒品
He doesn't run whore dens sell pirated CD nor coke
只开间小车房
He just runs a small garage
他根本不想做大买卖
He doesn't want his biz growing
大家都是龙虾叔的人
We're in the Lobster's gang
你看人家四大天王多酷
Look at the gangsters of Four Kings
十二点后， 这里我作主！
After midnight, I'm the master!
多酷， 我们琛哥...
So cool. Look at Sam...
有什么了不起？
Is he a big name?
二十四小时， 这里都是我作主！
All day, I'm the master here!
琛哥， 我们不是不想干， 是没得干
It isn't us who don't work but there's no jobs left
我们跟你， 是想干黑社会
We just want to be the gangsters
不是来修理汽车
Not technicians
修理汽车也可以是黑社会嘛
Garage is also gang's biz
你别以为这里是普通车房
It isn't an ordinary garage
这里是全港黑社会的卧底中心
It's the pivot of the gang undercover in Hong Kong
我要负责监视附近几百个警署
I'm responsible for a thousand police stations nearby
你一个人， 怎监视几百个警署？
How can you keep a thousand police stations under surveillance?
别顶嘴！
Talk back!
每个警署都有我的卧底！
There're undercover agents in every police station!
谁是你的卧底？
Who're they?
这不能告诉你， 只我一人知道
I can't tell you I'm the only person knowing this secret
我死了， 他只能当警察， 当一辈子 可我们...
If I die, they'll be cops for the rest of the life But we...
下车！
Get off!
过来...
Come here...
她老公卖鱼星修车不给钱
Sean hasn't footed the car-repairing bill
我抓来他的老婆孩子， 逼他还钱
I take his wife and kids here to make him foot the bill
进去再说
Get in
关二爷， 求你保佑我想个好主意
May God of Kuan give me a good excuse
马上放了他们， 别吓坏小孩子
to release them Don't scare the children
顺利摆平这件事， 拜托...
and make the troubles go, thanks...
你老公卖鱼星... 敢欠我的钱
Your husband, Sean still owes us money
是不是想我们砍你 一 、 二 、 三... 三六...
You want us to chop you...
砍你十八块？
into a thousand pieces, right?
你样子好可怕呀
You look dreadful
阿星这傻小子
It's Sean who
欠债不还， 当然不行
didn't foot the bill. It's his fault
要打打， 打屁股， 打手手
We must punish him
怎么样？不可怕吧
How's it? It isn't dreadful, right?
大哥， 你这样他们不会怕的
Bro, this doesn't work
吓坏小孩， 他们会屁滚尿流
What if the children are scared and then piss or shit here?
到头来还是要你清理
And it's you who do the cleaning
带他们出去玩...
Take them out...
买雪糕给他们吃
and buy them ice-cream
再给他们买玩具
and also toys
带他们去游乐场
Then bring them to the playground
沙田不好玩， 带他们过深圳
Any place is OK
女人， 快还钱！
Foot the bill!
信不信我剥光你的衣服， 拍你裸照
Or I tear your clothes to take some nude pix
再发给各大报刊杂志登封面？
Then use them as cover of porno magazines
真的？
Really?
怎么样， 这姿势？
How about this pose?
这姿势... 我学很久了
I've learnt it for a long time
怎样？行吗？
Does it look good?
不行... 我老婆快回来了
No... my darling's coming back
你想害死我呀？
You want me divorce?
你不怕丢脸吗？
It's dishonorable to be porno mag cover girl, isn't it?
丢脸？
Dishonorable?
没封面登才丢脸
If I can't be the cover girl it's really dishonorable
以前卖鱼星骗我， 说认识很多导演
My husband lied to me He said he knew many directors
还说让我拍三级片
and recommended me to be the actress of the 18-rated films
所以我才嫁给他
So I married him
其实， 我的身材... 是挺棒的
In fact, I have... a very good figure
不信， 你看看样板
Do take a look at my figure
行了... 回去等通知吧
OK... I'll call you
我会找你...
I'll call you...
请留个电话
Leave your phone number
琛哥
Bro Sam
我们不再跟你了
I quit your gang
什么？ 我们去跟四大天王！
What's wrong? I join the gangs of Four Kings!
你们一定会后悔！后悔莫及！
You'll be sorry! Very sorry!
深圳金劳强介绍我们来跟你的
Roy of Shenzhen introduced us to you
跟我？
You wanna join my gang?
不是想套我吧？
Wanna spy on me?
要套也套四大天王啦
If so, we'd joined the gangs of Four Kings
那跟刘德华好了， 跟我干嘛？
Join Diamond's gang why do you join my gang?
我想他误会了
I think he misunderstood us
那你再想个开场白吧
Then change the lead-in
想到了没有？
Is that OK?
想到了， 其实人人都想跟你， 琛哥
Got it... In fact many people wanna join your gang
一来可以加入黑社会
First, to be a gangster
二来可以学修车
Second, to learn car-repairing
再加上你这身打扮 你看... 还有朵花呢
And the way of your dressing... Look... at this blossom
试问谁不跟你的衣着？
Who won't imitate your way of dressing?
有品味
Good taste
我们只想做小混混， 不想做杀手
In fact, we only wanna be gangster not fighter
有见地
Clever
你怎么不说话？
How about you?
金劳成常说傻的才跟琛哥
Roy always says those fey will join Sam's gang
我是傻的， 当然跟你啦
I'm fey, so I got to join your gang
傻得可以
You're dreadfully fey
琛哥， 是那个
That one, Bro Sam
我是琛哥
Sam's speaking
老公， 快派人来减肥中心
Honey, send some people to the salon
四大天王的老婆在这里搞事呀
Four Kings' wives play tyrant here
随她们吧， 我改天跟她们老公说
Let them go I'll talk with Four Kings some day
不行， 她们说我卖假货， 要分我财产
No. They said I sold fake goods and requested the salon as compensation
这还得了？
How come they make a scene like this?
好， 我马上带一百几十人来... 摆平她们
OK, I'll bring a hundred people to make them go
琛哥， 不等你那一百几十人？
Should we wait for your gangsters Bro Sam?
你一百... 你几十... 你是人
You all are those a hundred gangsters
不就是一百几十人嘛， 走吧
We're ready to go
你肯收我们？
You admit our gang affiliation?
当作是吧
OK
那我们要不要谈谈？ 是呀
Should we talk about this first? Right...
也好
Fine
好不好？        好！
OK? Great!
照办
Go ahead
我们女人事情自己解决
It's better for us women to shoot it out on our own
叫你老公来干什么？
You called your husband to come here for what?
他又不是四大天王
He isn't one of Four Kings
我们只不过要你赔七年会费
We just ask for seven-year membership fee
另外加七个全包宴
Plus seven comprehensive packages
包纤腰 、 包丰胸 、 包肥臀 、 包无皺纹
With hour-glass abdomen and skin-resurfacing included
包三百小时免费按摩
And free three-hundred-hour massage
修甲 、 整发 、 磨脚皮
with manicure, hair-styling and feet peeling included
任何时间都可以做， 你明白吗？
Any time's available. Get it?
另外， 收缩水任搽， 丰胸水任用
And free toner and breast enlargement solution
这两种药水不可以乱用的
These two solution must be used with special care
不用你管！
None of your business!
我喜欢变成大波霸是我的事
I like D cup size, so what?
总之， 你这里的药水任我用
Remember... we can use any products we like
职员任点 、 任使 、 任劳 、 任怨
All the staff gotta serve us as we like
还有， 送 『运通宝』 和感冒茶
And also the women supplement and herbal tea pills
要大量
A large quantity
要知道我们老公四大天王
You should know our husbands get sick easily
常常生病， 没有感冒茶怎么办？
What should we do without herbal tea pills?
要知道 我们女人调理身体 『运通宝』 最好
You should know the women supplement's best to us
当然
Certainly
那岂不是整个店子都归你？
That means you own this salon?
让我们老公知道， 定给你来个大装修
If our husband knows this case they'll do graffiti here
到时吓跑客人就不好了
If so, it's no good to drive away the customers
你们不要恶人先告状吧
Don't make a scene like that
你们常常打我的职员
You've beaten my staff
我还没跟你们计较
I haven't made a claim on you
我们对她们不知多好
We've treated them very well
是她们自己不小心摔倒的
It's them who fell carelessly
不信， 你问问她们
You may ask them
是不是？
You fell carelessly?
是
Right
我们是不是对你们很好？
We treated you very well, right?
是
Yes
老公打电话来了
It's my husband
接电话这粗重功夫让我来吧
Let me do his kind of tough job for you
靓汤哥！
Tom!
你好， 我是琛仔呀
Hello, it's Sam
四位嫂子在我这里， 是
They're in my salon
一定满意， 包在我身上
They'll be satisfied with the service Trust me
包我身上， 行， 好
Count on me, OK?
你要真包得起才说
Can you?
老公， 她们蛮不讲理
Honey, they play tyrant here
说什么？再说扁死你！
What did you say? Mind your tits!
各位嫂子， 请息怒
Calm down, please
我刚从机场接回几位 泰国水疗按摩技师
I've just hired some Thai masseuses
马上为你们丰胸减肥
They'll do massage and chiropractic for you
包你们满意
You'll be satisfied with the service
你们好！
Hello!
我是水琼琼
I'm Nataly
我是水蜜蜜
I'm Dyran
我是水晶晶
I'm Ales
我们是...
We're...
魔幻天使三人组
Sam's Angels
试过我们... 正宗泰国手艺
Have you tried the authentic Thai-style massage?
包你死去活来...
You'll definitely have unbelievable fun
别再说了， 快给她们拆骨
No more talking. Give them punches
不... 是松骨
No... Give them fun
遵命
Yes, sir
四位阿嫂， 请跟我们来
This way, please
按摩按摩
Massage
各位嫂子， 好好享受...
Enjoy yourself...
舒舒服服 、 轻轻松松
and relax
这三个 “人妖打排球” 哪里找来的？
Where're these three transgirls from?
人家去泰国运毒， 我去泰国找人妖
People go Thailand for coke but transgirls to me
吴君如介绍的
Sandra Ng told me about them
你认识吴君如？
You know Sandra Ng?
我认识她男朋友
I know his boyfriend
小时候住在泰国， 长大留学美国
He moved to Thailand and studied in America
现在回来搞娱乐
Now he's back to make films
陈可辛吗？        就是他
You mean Peter Chan, right? Yes, Peter Chan
苳姐呢？
Where's Doris?
她有特殊疗程
She has a special treatment
在特殊房间里
In a special guest room
什么来的？
What's that?
爆水管
Water pipe cracks
爆水管？
Water pipe cracks?
那边怎么不爆？
Why don't those water pipes crack?
那边不爆吗？
They don't?
也爆！
They do!
爆水管， 怎么会有金鱼？
Why is there a goldfish?
是这样
Pipe cracks
三位太太好
Nice to see you again
现在我为你们介绍我国最新发明
Let me introduce you the latest technology of Thailand:
清迈负离子光彩夺目速丰胸
Instant breast enlargement by ionic re-texturizing system and IPL
等一下会有镭射光射出来
The laser operates in a few minutes
所以你们要戴上奶罩
So you got to put on the bras
眼罩        眼罩
It's mask Mask
不然的话， 就会射爆你们
Otherwise, it hurts your eyes
怎么只有一边？
Why does it operate on my right breast only?
你说要大一点嘛， 太太
You want the breast larger
那先集中做这边， 稍后再做那边
I do the right breast first and then the left
准备...
Ready...
开始
Go
怎会这么痛？
What's wrong? It's very painful
白白嫩嫩， 孩子都这样嫩
Silky complexion as kids...
搞定了， 琛哥
It's alright, Bro Sam
搞定？        真的？
Alright? It is?
自己看看
You may take a look
小心我呀！
Watch out!
大开眼界！这次如愿了吧？
Great! Your dream comes true, right?
多谢你呀！
Thanks!
好开心呀！
Great!
都说正宗手艺... 一流！
I've said it's authentic Thai style... it's great
靓汤老婆阿苳呢？        是啊
Where's Doris? Oh, yes
她刚才用过丰胸水， 现在又用收缩水
She used the breast enlargement solution and then the toner
但我觉得你的收缩水好像过了期
But I think your toner's expired
她有点不对劲
Something wrong with her
你们这些王八蛋...
You bastard...
把我搞成这样
Your toner makes me like a dwarf
我决不会放过你们！
I won't let you go!
太太， 您慢走
Have a nice day
你们这次闯祸了
You've made troubles this time
你真的想我这样做？
You really want me to do this?
是
Yes
知不知道会有什么后果？
Do you know what's the outcome?
我知道
Yes
你这样做...
If you go on
会闹出多大事情， 你知道的
There'll be a lot troubles You should know that
回不了头
No U-turn
只要那男人好...
Once it's good for my man...
我做什么都无所谓
it's no big deal
龙虾今晚在BOB卡拉OK
Lobster's in BOB karaoke tonight
知道了
Got it
唱得好好...
Sing it too well...
吃葡萄吧
Have some grapes
很甜吧？当然， 我喂你吃的
Sweet? Of course, it's from me
我都有东西给你吃
I have something for you to eat too
当然， 我替你弄的， 好味吧？...
I made this for you Of course it's good...
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday!
好正点呀！
It's cool!
我的心...         怎么了？
My heart... What's the matter?
满汉全席？
Such a big meal
你知道什么事吧
You should know that
不关女人的事
None of her business
还说不关？
None of her business?
拿来
Give it to me
你点的？
You ordered this dish?
给你的...
It's for you...
聪明
Clever
各位大哥， 今天的事我一人承担
It's me who are responsible for whatever happened
聪明！最欣赏你这样
Clever! I just want you to say this
龙虾死了
Lobster's dead
龙永孝以后定要我们交数给他
Kelvin must collect the money from us directly
我们四个， 以后都不会交数给他
We fad four won't pay him from now onward
虾叔死了？！
Uncle Lobster's died?
怎么死的？
How did he die?
开心死的
Hyper state
他正在唱卡拉OK
He was singing karaoke
突然杀出一帮脱衣舞娘
Suddenly there're a group of nude women
高呼 “生日快乐”
crying Happy Birthday
他一把年纪， 没试过这么刺激
He was too old to be hyped up
心脏病发， 死了
He died of heart attack
虾叔今天生日？
Is it Uncle Lobster's birthday?
注定的， 那帮舞娘摸错门
It was his destiny Those nude women got the wrong place
阿孝来了
Kelvin's come
这么热闹？
Why are so funny?
座无虚席
No seat left
吃东西， 老顾客自会有座位
All regular customers have their own seats
今天我爸的事...
My dad's accident...
相信大家都很清楚
You all should know...
我爸生前说过
Dad had said
出来风流
Before enjoying the women
钞票先交
gotta pay first
今天我就想跟大家说说交钱的问题
I just wanna talk about the payment
太子， 节衰顺变
Take care, Kelvin
我们约了人打牌， 告辞
Excuse me I got to get together with friends
牛肉好新鲜， 慢慢吃
The beef's fresh. Try it
站住， 你们四个好像没交数
Wait a minute You four haven't paid me the quid in
我们一向交给虾叔
We used to pay to Uncle Lobster
现在交给我
You may pay to me now
我们想不出理由来说服自己
We can't figure out why I should pay to you
你抓走我们老婆？！
You've caught our wives?!
她们现在在货船上
They're on the cargo ship
今晚三点， 货船开往非洲莫桑比克
It sets off at 3 a. M and heads for Mozambique
想跑回来， 也要十天半个月
It takes at least ten to fourteen days to get back to Hong Kong
以为什么大不了的事
No big deal
你们不交数的话
If you don't pay to me
我今晚就放了她们
I'll set them free tonight
考虑一下吧
Think twice
想一想， 如果她们在非洲
Think: If they were in Africa
两个星期， 你们多自由
how free you'd be in these two weeks!
怎样放纵都可以
You can do whatever you want
如果我放她们走
If I set them free
到时你们就要过地狱般的生活
how poor you'd be at that time
太子... 万事好商量
Hey, let's have a conversation
我们有一点点要求...
But we have a request...
两个星期太少了
Two weeks is a very short period
三个星期怎么样？
How about three weeks?
是呀， 怎样？        行
How's it? OK
我用车送她们进森林， 再放下她们
We'll send them to the jungle and drop them off
找到路出来， 也要十天半个月
It takes at least two weeks to find the way out
好啊...
Great...
我明天一早就过数到你账上
I'll transfer the money to you tomorrow morning
我也是
Me too
大家这么开心， 一起干杯吧
Bottoms up
我们敬爸爸一杯！
Dad, cheers!
虾叔， 干杯！
Uncle Lobster, cheers!
对不起        不好意思
Sorry Excuse me
我们要牢记爸爸的话
You got to remember dad's words
出来风流， 钞票先交
Before enjoying the women gotta pay first
出来风流， 钞票先交！
我们今晚的任务
Tonight's duty is...
就是监视龙虾的接班人...
To watch closely the successors of Lobster
龙永孝和四大天王
Kelvin Long and Four Kings
他们今晚将与新冒头的曾琛 开秘密会议
They have a secret meeting with the nova, Sam
我已派人在里面偷拍偷听
I've sent agents to do secret shooting and recording
你们在电脑中可以看到
You may see them via computer
你的偷拍镜放在哪？
Where's your hidden camera?
你真行
You have your own way
你呢？
How about you?
鞭上
On the ponytail
你真行
You have your own way too
你呢？
How about you?
猜猜看
Guess it
Mandy， 请开电脑 我傅送画面给你看
Please turn on the computer, Mandy lmage transmitting
人人去快活， 他在服侍人
People enjoy the fun time and he serves them
再多看几分钟
Wait for a couple of minutes
阿琛...
Sam...
你说来了几个泰国妞， 人呢？
You've said there're Thai beauties Where're they?
来了...
Coming...
阿茵！
Yvonne!
你好！        你好...
Hello! Hello...
水蜜蜜， 水蜜蜜...
Ales and Dyren...
要不要验一下？
Do you take a look at them?
验一下好
Yeah, take a look
大哥， 交给我
Bro, let me do it for you
那... 你验阿茵
Well... check Yvonne
她验过了
I've checked her
验过？
You have?
交给你， 过来！
OK. It's your turn
怎样？
How're they?
AA+
好！
Great!
傻强， 胖子， 跟她去收货
Crazy Tom, Chubbie go pick them up with her
检查...
Have a check...
长官...
Sir...
劲姐， 长官干嘛？
Cool Lady, what's officer doing?
不知道， 可能是摩斯密码
I have no idea. Perhaps it's Morse Code
上！上... 顶住！
Go! Go... Hold it!
怎么搞的？
What's wrong?
就差一点点
Almost got it
他不是在傅摩斯密码吗？
Isn't he sending Morse Code?
什么密码？他在赌马
Code? He's decoding the Derby news
她们真是泰国妞？
Are they really Thai?
如假包换
Sure
这么白净？
They have fair complexion
漂亮吧
They're pretty, right?
怎么样？
How're they?
琛哥， 泰国妞已验收
Bro Sam, I've checked all the Thai hookers
叫傻强大声说
Tell Crazy Tom to cry
这些妞是他的！
All the hookers belong to him!
傻强， 琛哥叫你大声说
Crazy Tom, Bro Sam's told you to cry...
这些妞是你的
All the hookers belong to you
这些妞是你的！
All the hookers belong to me!
好热呀
It's hot
有内鬼， 终止咸湿
There're spies. Action terminated
大家听着...
Listen
有内鬼， 终止风流！
There're spies. Action terminated
怎么办？
What should we do?
傻强， 赶走那些妞
Drive the hookers off
大家跟我来
All of you follow me
准备工作
Get ready
五 、 六 、 七 、 八
5, 6, 7, 8
妹妹你坐船头， 哥哥在岸上走
On the sampan there is a lass on the shore there is a lad
恩恩爱爱牵绳荡悠悠
Blissful and daring
小妹妹， 坐船头
Lass on the sampan
哥哥你在岸上走
Lad on the shore
警官， 找我们有事吗？
Sir what's the matter?
你想参加？
You wanna join us?
来， 一起玩吧
Come. Let's play together
我又再次栽在阿琛手上
I lost to Sam again
我们从小到大都是同学和好朋友
We used to be good friends and classmates since we're children
可他用卑鄙手段 抢走我最心爱的女人Mandy
He stole my beloved Mandy by dirty tricks
所以我一定要搜集他的犯罪证据
So I must gather evidence of his criminal activities
抓他坐牢， 抢回Mandy
To cop him for any criminal offence and win Mandy back
是时候决定Mandy跟谁了
It's the right time to decide who wins Mandy
当然跟我！
It's me of course!
你俩好兄弟别为我翻脸吧
You two are good friends Don't quarrel over me
何兄何弟？谁是他兄弟？
Who said he's my friend?
你看， 他像个臭飞， 我可是班长
Look. He looks like a Teddy boy and I'm the prefect
你只能选一个， 不可能一人一半
You got to pick one of us
你是班长？
You're the prefect?
那你是什么？
And you're...
臭飞！当然是跟臭飞
Teddy boy, of course
臭飞生活才多姿多彩
Teddy boy's life's gorgeous
你看他， 整个傻蛋
Look at him. So dull
别管他， 我会把家管得很好
Leave him alone I'll keep the family well
我会把香港管得更好
I'll keep Hong Kong well
跟我吧， 我会让你开心
Go with me. I'll make you happy
这样吧
Well
谁先逗我笑， 我就跟谁
Who can make me laugh, I'll go with him
你先说吧
You first
好
OK
从前， 有个猎人在森林里...
Once upon a time in the forest there's a hunter
跟他老婆结了婚
marrying his wife
第二年， 他老婆生下小孩就死了
In the next year she died after the child was born
那猎人既要打猎， 又要带孩子
That hunter took care of the child while hunting
忙得团团转
He's extremely busy
于是他训练了一只狗
So he trained a loyal dog
狗不是用 “只” 来形容的
Loyal isn't used for dogs
是用 “条” 来形容的
It should be lying
你说你像你那条狗， 那就好笑了
You're funny enough if you say you're like that lying dog
你看
Look
这条狗的故事是我说的
The lying dog story is my idea
但你条狗出自我的口呀
But lying is my idea
赢了！
I win!
不服气？抽签吧
You aren't happy with this? Draw a lot
长赢还是短赢？
How to win? Longest? Shortest?
当然是长的赢
Longest of course
还不赢你？
I win, right?
你没见过真正的长傢伙， 看着
You don't know how long can a lot be? Look
没这么长吧？
It's so long
我不服！
I don't think you can win!
阿琛， 合胃口吗？
Does it what your appetite?
一扫而空
I ate them all
再来一个？
How about an extra one?
对我这么好...
How nice you're...
想告我什么罪？
What am I accused of?
没事， 查过你的酒吧， 很干净
Nothing. I've searched your pub It's a common pub
你随时可以走
You may go now
矮子
Dwarf
我惯了顺手一拨， 没想到...
I used to turn it in a casual manner Can't imagine...
没事... 帮你拿走菜条
It's alright I'll take away this vegetable
不用说这些
We're fine
你是大哥
You're Big Bro
大嫂来了        不会吧？
Mandy's come She has?
左边... 别看！
On the left... Don't look!
现在怎办？
What should I do?
什么都别想， 一个字...
Just concentrate on one word...
酷
Smart
刘德华
Tom Cruise
操！这个是万梓良
Shit! It's Sean Connery
算了， 你还是对着他说吧
Forget it. You'd better tell him
告诉你， 算你走运
I tell you, you're in good luck
我娶了老婆， 人已改变
My life after marriage is different
以前？早就一拳打死你！
In the past, I'd beaten you up!
老公... 走啦
Honey... Let's go
老婆， 你...
Darling, you...
干嘛？        走开点！
What's the matter? Go away!
Mandy， 我也不想你不开心
I don't want you to be miserable, Mandy
你嫁阿琛前， 我已说过他很烂滚
I've already told you Sam isn't a faithful husband
他现在是我老公嘛        就是
But he's my husband now That is!
我放了张牌在你口袋
I've put a piece of playing card in your pocket
我放了副牌在你口袋
I've put a pack of playing card in your pocket
我放整副麻雀在你口袋！
I've put a set of mahjong in your pocket!
你吹牛
Bullshit
阿琛， 你好自为之
Mind your p's and q's
别栽在我手里
Don't fall into my hands
你一旦坐牢或挂掉...
If you're behind bars or die
Mandy就会重投我怀抱
I'll win Mandy back
你太不像话， 舌头都伸出来
You're too much You stretch the tongue out
老婆， 走！
Go, darling!
你看我们， 多可怜多凄惨
Look at us. So poor
岂有此理！在我面前泡师姐？
Too bad! You wanna date the policewomen?
给我弹出去！
Hop!
警察可以乱打人吗？
How can a police officer beat people without grounds?
我不是警察， 我是条子！
I'm not a police officer but a cop!
条子也不可打人！
Cops can't beat people without grounds?
我是条子， 你们不是人， 是人渣！
But you aren't human but trash
走就走嘛
I go
往哪走？
Where should we go?
还打...
Don't fight
笑什么？
What are you laughing?
我没叫你们走， 是叫你们弹出去！
I've told you to hop, not go!
弹就弹！
Alright!
你真的弹？
You do hop?
弹呀！
Hop!
臭小子， 敢搞我女儿
Wanna screw my daughter
非教训他们不可
I got to give them a lesson
只有一个想搞你女儿
But only one of them is interested in your daughter
其他两个想搞我们
the other two are interested in us
那更该打
Then they're even worse
我女儿这么正不搞， 搞你们？
They don't appreciate my daughter!
长官
Sir
对了， 我跟你说
Tell you something...
现在门口站着三个王八蛋
There're three rascals outside
他们是你牛叔的杀父仇人
They're public enemies
你吩咐手足们， 有空没空都搞搞他们
Tell all the fellows search them from time to time
有事开两枪， 没事揍三拳
Give them two shoots or three punches if necessary
但那三个王八已经进了报案室
But they've already got into the report room
警官， 是这样的
Sir...
我们的心被人偷走了
Our hearts are stolen
那偷心贼就躲在警署里
And the one who stole our hearts are in the police station
长官， 他们耍花样
They fool us, sir
傻的也知道
Everybody knows this
你以为我这三条杠是捡回来的？
You think it's a coincidence that I got promoted to sergeant
报假案浪费警力， 一样要坐牢
The offence of false reporting is subject to the imprisonment
警官！告不告由得你作主吗？
It isn't you who make the decision, sir!
是由律政处决定的， 你当我白痴呀？
Only the Department of Justice has the say. You think we're plain stupid?
我们也是警察...
We're cops...
故事的拥趸
Cops' fans
两个老婆， 两个子女
Two wives, two children
我爱香港！
I love Hong Kong!
凭自我， 硬汉子
Here's a tough bloke
拼出一身痴！
Fighting for a heart!
好大的一条龙虾！
A lobster
你的心在哪？
Where's your heart?
我的心被个师姐偷走了
My heart's stolen by a policewoman
你呢， 胖子， 你的心怎样？
How about your heart? What does it look like?
我很粗的
It's big
我是说我的心， 师姐
I mean my heart, madam
我很粗心的
I have a big heart
你的心是怎样的？
How does your heart look like?
啊！
Well
我的心...
lt...
我的心呢...
It...
我的心...
里...
My...
心里...
My heart
有个...
hides a...
谜
secret...
难解， 难计
To be unveiled...
心里心里这个谜
My heart hides a secret
藏在心底
Holding me tightly
这个这个心里谜
This secret in my heart...
完全是围着你
Is all about you
这个这个心里谜
This secret in my heart...
常令我入迷
Makes me faint
愿爱似花， 在我心中
May the love in my heart
放出璀璨， 放出美丽
sparkles like firework
为你相思， 为你着迷
That rejuvenates my life
我心深里， 爱得美丽
In the valley of my heart
请你请你解那谜
I get lost in the maze
莫再将情深埋
It's you who
开放心底让我迷
can lead me out...
迷尽一世
Out of the maze
请你请你解那...
Please...
请够了没有？
Please wake up!
律政处有指示
The Department of Justice
放了来警署泡妞那三个傢伙
instructed us to release the blokes aiming at dating
那不便宜了他们？
Let them off?
不会， 他们是车房琛的人
It isn't be the case They're from Sam's gang
把这三人从羁留所押出来
Release them first
再去四大天王的舞厅里
and then send them to Four Kings' night club
找四大天王卖毒品
for the acid
行不通的
It doesn't work
我就住靓汤楼上
Tom and I live in the same building
雪柜和靓妹常到我家来
Sharon and Leila usually visit me
他一定知道我们是女警
They should already know we're cops
决不会卖毒品给我们的
They won't sell us the acid
他知道你们是警察， 更想玩弄你们
If he knows that he may wanna hoax you
我就不信他不会失手
I don't think he won't fall
那岂不很危险？
That's dangerous, isn't that?
对， 有危就有机
Yeah, but there's an opportunity
你和华弟假扮情侣， 候命支援
Watson and Cold Lady imitate a couple for back-up
谢谢
Thank you!
遵命
Yes, sir
师姐， 别占便宜
Don't paw me, please
胖子， 这房间不是人人可以进来的
Chubbie, this room is restricted
上次我说是李嘉诚的儿子 都不让我进
Even I said I was the son of Lee Ka-shing but I couldn't get in
靓汤哥， 我有几个... 大学同学
Tom, these are my university schoolmates
从荷兰回来的
from Holland
那怎么样？
What do you mean?
好麻烦
They're troublesome
她们说想尝尝 “香港糖” 你说多老土
They wanna try acid sugar So obsolete, right?
有没有货？
Do you have any acid?
很重牛奶味
Milk-flavored
还热呢
It's freshly made
那... 多少钱？
How... how much?
喜欢就拿去吧
No need to pay
走吧...
Go...
你们已经被捕
Cops
你们藏有和贩卖危险药品
I'm placing you under arrest For alleged possession of Class A drugs
非必要事不需说
You have the right to remain silent
但你所说的将成为呈堂证供
Any statement you make may be used as evidence in trial by court-martial
小丫头， 叔叔住你楼下几十年了
Both of us live in the same building for years, bitch
你不认得我啦？
You don't recognize me?
居然跑来放蛇？
Wanna spy on me?
对不起， 我是警察
Sorry. We're cops
对不起
Sorry
那包是嘀答糖
Those are sweets only
警察抓人， 好怕呀...
Wanna cop me? It's horrible...
这就简单了
That's easy
我整理一下
Let me draw a conclusion
我们不知道她们是警察
We don't know they're cops
她们现在抓不到人
They can't cop you
而靓汤哥也没有贩毒
And Tom doesn't posse any acid
那就是...         没事
That's it... Nothing
跳舞吧！
Let's dance!
等等！
Wait a minute!
敢在太岁头上动土？
You dare wake up a sleeping dog?
三个走， 三个留下， 你们自己挑
Only three of you can go Make the decision on your own
她们打摩斯密码上来 说被人押往后巷
They're escorted to the side lane And they asked for help via Morse Code
走！
Action!
不用急
Wait a minute
我们居高临下， 有情况也一目瞭然
We're in the best position to watch them
真是出了事， 再去救她们也不迟
If anything goes wrong we can make it on time
那倒是
That's true
知不知道拒捕袭警罪行很严重？
Do you know assault on police officer is a serious crime?
废话！走呀！
Bullshit! Go!
出事了！
Shit!
救人！
Action!
你们都中招！
You two lost too!
走呀华弟！
Go, Watson!
别看着我！
Don't look at me!
你不是说要去救人吗？
You've said you'll take action haven't you?
我们还不去？
Why don't we go?
你浑身湿透， 怎么救人？
You get wet. How can you save them?
被人看到就不好了
It's no good if somebody sees you
剥光你衣服！
Tear your clothes off!
别搞她！
Don't screw her!
不搞她搞谁？
Who should I screw if I don't screw her?
傻瓜， 这还不知道？
You don't know about AA Night Club?
佳时桑拿， 现在重新装修
AA Night Club is newly renovated
特价酬宾周
Special offer is given
两个钟加代支只不过三百二十八元
Three hundred something for two hours
冰火七重天 、 电动独龙钻不在话下
Blowjob, ass blow
还有最新的牛奶洗啷啷
and some innovations
说是肥晶介绍的还有九折
10% discount if you're referred by Jing
还不快去佳时桑拿舒服一下？
Why don't you act now?
走吧
Let's go
不， 大哥， 我们不拍写真啦？
Bro, we don't take the nude pix?
差点中计， 先搞定这三个
Right. It's better to take the pix first
淫贼！不许你们调戏良家妇女！
Stop it! Don't screw the innocent ladies!
这三个什么东西？
Who're you?
我们就是...
We're...
皮蛋... 黑侠！
SEMARU... SUKA!
大哥， 他们是傻子
Big Bro, they're just idiots
他们真是傻子， 不怕子弹？
Three idiots. They don't fear bullets?
跟我说子弹？
Bullets?
我连砖块都不怕！
I don't even fear the bricks!
怕了吧？
Just a tiny little bullet
求求你... 别逗我们笑...
Please... don't be so silly...
求我了？
Please?
扁他！
Beat him!
风！        雷！
Wind! Thunder!
电！
Light!
胖子， 我在后面掩护你， 去吧
Chubbie, go. I'll cover you at the back
你那个是什么电？
Who's who?
不知道
I don't know
别玩啦！
Don't fool us!
那你玩吧
Then you fool them
三位大哥... 别杀我们
Please... don't kill us
怕了吗？
You scare us?
你们要这三个妞...
You just want these three gals...
我放她们跟你们走
I release them
听语气好像由你作主
It sounds like you're the master
我偏让你两个手下先走
I let your gangsters go first
两个混蛋！你们好没义气！
You two rascal! You two have no loyalty to me
饶命... 胖子， 怎样？
Please... What should we do, Chubbie?
动手        好呀
Go ahead Fine
他呀        我？
He... Me?
你想怎样... 胖哥哥？
What do you want, Bro Chubbie?
拍照， 脱衣服！
Take some pix. Take off your clothes!
去抓人
Catch them
等等
Wait
我这样子怎么抓？
How can I catch them without outfit?
你舍得啦？
You really accept this?
舍不得...
No...
那怎样？
Then?
走
Go
开心点， 笑笑， 挺胸
Cheers. And pull the boobs up
对， 挺胸
Right, pull the boobs up
几位小姐， 我的车就停在外面
Vehicles are ready, ladies
不如上我的车走吧
Let's go
现在小巴真好
The minibus service's pretty good
有空调， 又舒服
Air-conditioned and comfortable
二十四小时通车
Twenty-four-hour service
乘客又斯文        就是
The passengers are gentle That's it
大叔， 好了， 你看够没有？
Can you stop looking at me?
我们已经够尴尬了
It's embarrassing
随便瞎扯都没话说了
I've said whatever I can
你还想怎样？
What do you want?
皮蛋先生
Mr. Semaru
谢谢你们今晚救了我们三个
Thanks for saving us
你别这么说
It doesn't matter
“皮蛋” 不是我们的真名
SERMARU SUKA isn't our real name
那可否告诉我们真名字？
Can you tell us your real name?
不行， 我们真名比假名还难听
No. Our real name's much worse
那给我们看看真面目吧
Then let us see your face
我们真面目比假的更难看
Our face's really nasty
你们都没诚意做朋友
You don't wanna be our friends
你当我们三个是朋友？
You think we're friends?
你们奋不顾身救了我们三个
You saved us
若不当你们是朋友， 我们还是人吗？
How come we don't see you as friends?
说起来， 那三个一走了之， 真不是人
Those three blokes left us alone They're our enemies
不管多细心好心， 都是假惺惺
They are just hypocritical
不说那三个了
Forget about them
说你们的真名吧
What's your real name?
我叫肥抽
I'm Chubbie
我叫阿强
I'm Tom
我叫...
I'm...
你不说就算了， 坏蛋
If you don't tell us, forget about that bastard
好厉害， 让你猜中了
You're great. How can you get it?
我真的叫坏蛋呀
My real name's Bastard
真的叫坏蛋？
It is?
是呀， 我老爸很讨厌我
Yes, my dad hated me
给我取了个惹笑名字
So he gave me this name
现在终于被人取笑了
Now everybody laughs at me
好了， 知道你们的真名
We know your real names
让我们看看真面目吧
Then let us see your face
真的要看？
You really wanna see?
又是这三个！
It's you again!
我早说别脱下头套嘛
I've said don't take off the masks
一脱下就出事了
Once we took it off, there was accident
别埋怨了， 走吧
Don't blame. Let's go
坏蛋， 我们明天放假
Bastard, we're off tomorrow
放假？
Off tomorrow?
那我明天来搞你...
Then we screw you tomorrow...
不， 来看你
Nope... see you tomorrow
好， 明天两点
See you at two in the afternoon
我想我已经堕入爱河...
I think I've fallen in love...
我也堕入爱河了...
I've fallen in love...
河了...
Love...
今天我约了1984年旺角...
I've made an appointment...
叱吒最受欢迎小白脸大奖得主大碌叔
with the most popular pimp
同年他还夺得劲爆金鸟奖
who won numerous gals and awards
以及十大泡妞其中七大奖项
of winning numerous beauties
他以一招 “洗干净便没事”
His famous “lt's Alright”
还夺得四台联颁 『全球华人至尊无情无义大奖』
Won award of the year
听这名衔就知道他是个泡妞高手
We can know he's good at winning gals
你真厉害， 都能记得住
You're great. You can memorize these all
他才厉害， 所有奖都拿
Actually it's he who's great and got all the awards
等等， 不知我妈有没有中招？
Wait a minute Did my mum lose her heart to him?
胖子， 听你这么说...
Chubbie...
看来有点像呀
Perhaps you mum did
别玩啦
Don't fool us
这位就是我舅舅大碌叔！
This is my uncle!
长得帅不帅？
Is he handsome?
时间真是帅哥的最大敌人
To the handsome blokes time's their enemy
怎样？想我教你们什么泡妞招数？
What do you want to know?
是这样的， 舅舅
Uncle...
我们约了三个妞去别墅派对
We've dated three gals
想请教你有什么快招
tell us the shortcut to win them
有样东西， 叫 “淫贱不能移”
This is lasciviousness
曹查理年代用到现在啦
It's used in the old days
我们想玩真感情呀
We want true love
你可不可以别这么落伍？
You'd better keep yourself updated
有志气！
Such an aspirant!
介绍样新产品给你们
Let me introduce you something
运通宝... 不， 是 “我爱碧咸” ！
This one is... adoration!
我爱碧咸？
Adoration?
你们跟心上人谈情之前
Before you see the gals
用这喷喷自己的脸 、 舌头
Spray it on the face or tongue
女孩子一闻到...
If gals smell it...
立刻觉得你英俊十倍
They'll think you're tens times more handsome than before
简直跟碧咸一样
You all look like David Beckham
舅舅， 你的大恩大德 我死全家也铭记于心
I won't forget your generosity
不用客气， 多谢八千块
It's eight thousand, thanks
三个混蛋到哪去了？
Where do the three bastard go?
我早叫你帮我别帮他们
I've told you not to give them a helping hand
好在我卖给他们的 “我爱碧咸” 是假货
Those adoration is fake
其实还是曹查理的 “淫贱不能移”
It's lasciviousness
他们用了， 定被师姐们揍扁
They'll be beaten by those policewomen if they use it
那我们就黄雀在后了
Then we can grasp this chance
最近有什么好东西？
Any new and cool product?
当然有
Certainly
这就是荷兰最厉害的迷晕药
This is the coolest coma-inducing drug from Holland
叫做 “八步半”
It's Eight-and-a-half-steps
八步半？
Eight-and-a-half-steps?
好像电影名字
It sounds like the name of films
你知道我最热爱电影
You should know I'm a cinema-goer
这是纪念我偶像费利里的
This is to commemorate my idol Fellini
女孩被这飞针射中， 不出九步便晕倒
Gals'll be in coma within nine steps if they're stuck by these needles
这么厉害？
Really?
承惠两万
Twenty thousand, thanks
两万？太贵了吧
Twenty thousand? So expensive
有东西送的
And a gift offered
加送一瓶 “我爱朱茵” 给你
This is adoration V.2
什么来的？
What's that?
若不幸泡上个猪排啃不下
If you meet a hag
就喷喷自己
Just spray out all over your face
便自然觉得对方像朱茵了
You'll find they look like Britney Spears
早上田鸡才来买走一箱
Timmy bought a carton of adoration V.2 this morning
说是周星驰要的
For his boss, Stephen Chow
我劝他算了， 过去的别再想了
I told him to forget about the past
还不是曹查理的玩意？
These are the same as that adoration, right?
看开点吧， 混口饭吃
Just earn a crust
胖子， 你干什么？
What are you doing, Chubbie?
又鸡又鸭， 你搞什么呀？
Chicken and duck. It's a big meal
随便青菜白饭不就行了
Just prepare some vegetables and rice
知道原因吗？
Why?
我们有 “我爱碧咸”
We have adoration
到时候她们就会爱死我们
They'll lose their hearts to us
何必搞这么多花样？
It's no use to do this kind of tricks
对呀
Right
她们爱我们 我们该对她们做些什么？
They love us. What should we do then?
你说呢？
What do you think?
你猜猜
Guess it
打麻将！她们一定放牌
Playing mahjong They must give us a chance
别闹， 来了
Don't waste time. They've come
嗨， 宝贝！
Hi! Baby!
噢， 大柠乐！
Oh! Shit!
对不起， 我爸坚持要跟着来
Sorry. My dad insists on his presence
你们不介意吧？
Do you mind?
不介意！
No, we don't
开心死啦！
It's our honour!
有东西吃？
Some food ready?
是呀， 有东西吃
Oh yes, the food is ready
你随便吃吧
Help yourself
我们出去聊聊
We go out for a chat
爸， 我们出去一下
Dad, we go out for a while
不行！
Oh, no
他在这里， 当然不行
He's here. We can't make it
怎么了？
How's it?
他... 他一个人闷嘛
He... he... is bored
没关系， 你们陪他玩一会
It doesn't matter You may entertain him first
晚一点才陪我们吧
and then entertain us later
晚一点？
Later?
好！就凭你这句 “晚一点”
Alright just for this sentence
我们陪他玩！
I play with him first!
笑什么？摸牌吧
What're you laughing at? Draw a tile
怎样？随便打一张你都死
How's it? You'll lose to me for any tile
打错了！
Wrong number
我捡了张牌， 怎办？
I pick the tile But what should we do now?
算我吃亏点， 再来一局
It doesn't matter. One round more
这可不是办法
It doesn't work
我整份工资都给他了 他还碍手碍脚！
All my salary's paid to him But he's still here
那怎么样？
What should we do?
砍了他！
Kill him!
他是警察呀
He's a cop
警察？我也是警察！
Cop? Me too!
谁知道？
Who knows?
你们三个当然想我走
Of course, you three want me to go
不是！
No!
不是？虚伪！
No? How sham you're!
长官， 够了， 放过我们吧
That's enough, sir. Give us a chance
放条生路行吗？
Just a chance, OK?
好， 放条生路给你们没问题
OK. I give you a chance
若你们通过我用测谎机测谎 且令我满意
If you pass the lie detection tests with good result
就放条生路给你们， 我搭的士走
I give you a chance and I'll go at once
好！
OK!
牛叔， 要这么多电线吗？
Uncle, why are here so many wires?
这里也有
And here's a wire too
是呀
Yes
不如算了
Or don't do the test
叽叽喳喳干嘛？坐下！
Still bullshit. Sit down!
我现在问问题， 你们要凭良心回答
Now I ask you questions You got to answer them honestly
不然就会后悔
Otherwise, you'll repent
先问你
You first
有没有嫖妓？
Do you patronize hookers?
没有！
Nope!
怎么会这样？
Why is it like this?
你们其中有个人撒谎
If one of your squad lies to me
其他两个就会触电
The other two will get an electric shock
谎言越大， 电压就越强
The bigger the lies the higher the voltage
好， 我先说
Well, I start
我从来不撒谎！
I never tell lies!
你这混蛋！        怎么样？
You bastard! So what?
好， 你们干哪行？
Well, what do you do?
黑社会
Gangster
大声点
Louder
黑社会！
Gangster!
这么大声干嘛？想电死我们呀？
Why have you spoken so loudly? You want us dead?
牛叔， 我爸是李嘉诚， 我妈是杨紫琼
Uncle, my dad's Li Ka-shing and my mum's Michelle Yeoh
我女朋友是刘嘉玲！
My girlfriend's Carina Lau!
搬刘嘉玲出来？
Carina Lau?
牛叔， 我不爱雪柜
Uncle I don't love Sharon
我爱你！
and I love you!
我没说刘嘉玲呀！
I don't say Carina Lau!
我还有话要问
I still got some questions
你今天约会我女儿， 有何企图？
Why do you invite my daughter to here?
我警告你， 小心说话
Mind your words
我...
I...
其实， 我...
Actually, I...
就...
date...
约了Angel...
Angel...
... 她
just to
谈心事
have a chat
谈完心事又怎样？
Then?
谈完了...
Then...
当然谈... 我的抱负
we surly talk about my aspiration
就我个人来说...
To me...
Angel是我一生中最爱的女人
Angel's the most daring woman in my life
我不会再爱另一个
I don't love another one
但是爱归爱， 男儿志比天高
But a man must be an aspirant
我爱她之余...
Besides loving her...
还想跟她同心协力， 改造香港黑社会
I must work with her to put the gangsters to the right track
共创美好明天， 将他们改邪归正
For our prosperous future
我爱香港！
I love Hong Kong!
好！        多谢
Great! Thank you
你看， 没有触电
Look! They don't get shocked
到时我会购置两幢房屋给你
At that time, I'll buy you two houses
我会跟你女儿结婚生子
I'll marry your daughter and raise children with her
到时你追孙子 、 孙子追小狗 、 小狗追皮球...
At that time, let's play the ball with the dogs and cats
皮球滚到我身上， 我再抛给你
The balls reach me and I throw the ball to you
天伦之乐， 乐也融融
What a bliss of a family
好甜蜜呀
So sweet
轮到你
It's your turn
你是否很想哄靓妹上床？
You wanna have Leila to sleep with you?
是
Yes
但我想哄她自己上床
But I hope she sleeps on her own
她日夜工作， 实在太辛苦
She works day and night. So poor
睡眠不足 引致内分泌失调是女人大忌
Once she doesn't have enough sleep she'll get sick easily
所以我只想一边唱情歌 一边哄她睡觉
So I wanna sing love songs to make her sleep sweetly
一边唱 、 一边哄...
I sing the love songs...
让她睡个好觉
She'll have a sweet dream
他真的好疼我啊
He really cares me
轮到你
It's your turn
你是否很想跟雪柜发生婚前性行为？
You wanna have pre-marital sex with Sharon?
当然不是
Definitely not
于我个人来说...
To me...
我是不会计较雪柜以前的感情生活
I don't care about Sharon's past history
至于婚前性行为...
For the pre-marital sex...
我更加极力反对
I strongly object it
况且...
And...
其实我还是一个处男
I don't have any sex experience
好啊
Great
我没试过处男呀
I haven't had sex with virgin male
这部机一定有毛病
Something wrong with the machine
没办法， 我决定大义灭亲！
I got no way so I have to ignore the filial piety
了不起！
Great!
等等！
Wait a minute!
给我们一分钟
Wait one more minute
出来！
Come out!
干什么？
What're you doing?
出来呀！
Come out!
干嘛？
What're you doing?
“我爱碧咸” ， 你们忘了？
Adoration. You forget this one?
现在她们这么爱我们
Now they adore us
还用 “我爱碧咸” 干嘛？ 对呀
We use this for what? True
你干嘛？        不知道
What're you doing? Beats me
你干嘛？
What're you doing?
不知道
Beats me
我的宝贝...
Say my name...
你干什么！
What're you doing?
我只知道我很想摸你们胸部
I just wanna feel your breast
我也是呀        我都是
Me too Me too
分我一份
Give me my part
救命呀！
Help!
快找人救我们
Anybody here? Help!
救命呀！
Help!
救命...
Help...
这么疯狂？
Why are they so crazy?
动手！
Action!
一 、 二 、 三 、 四
1, 2, 3, 4...
五... 六... 七... 八...
5... 6... 7... 8...
行呀， 继续
It works. Go ahead
你们想干嘛？
What do you want?
打倒他们！
Shoot them down!
这不是 “八步半” 吗？
This is Eight-and-a-half-steps, isn't?
那会怎样？
So?
中了再走八步半就会晕倒
After you get stuck you'll lose consciousness in nine steps
我跟他们拼了！
I fight against them!
一 、 二 、 三 、 四 、 五 、 六 、 七 、 八...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
抬起他！
Lift him up!
怎么办？        别动！
What should we do? Don't move!
什么？        你还动？
What? DON'T MOVE!
我背你上去
I carry you upstairs
这步算不算？
Is this step included?
喝得烂醉也能浇醒
Even shower does wake up those drunkard
不信这区区 “八步半” 浇不醒
I do think it works for Eight-and-a-half-steps
浇冷水看看
Take a shower
有人来了， 我去把门顶着
They're outside. I guard the door
开门...
Open the door...
哪个三八打我？
Who the hell hit me?
开门...
Open the door...
朋友， 我帮你拿枪
Man, I help you take this pistol
劳驾        不客气
Thanks Welcome
你是谁？
Who're you?
我是警察！
Cop!
拦着他！
Stop him!
岂有此理！敢袭警？
Shit! Assault on the police!
我爱朱茵？
Adoration V.2?
进去！
Get in!
进去！看什么？
Get in! What're you looking at?
进去！
Get in!
只剩一步， 怎么办？
One step left. What should I do?
朱...         朱茵！
Britney... Britney Spears!
你们别过来， 我不是朱茵
Freeze. I'm not Britney Spears
没动静？
No response?
把门反锁就行了
Just lock the door
你怎么样？
How are you?
干嘛？
What's wrong?
又来？
Lost controlled again?
不可以这样...
I shouldn't lose the self-control...
但我控制不了自己， 怎么办？
No, I can't. What should I do?
不用控制啦
No need to control then
明白， 靓汤挂了
Got it. Tom's mad
还剩下其他三个... 和车房琛
Only three Kings and Sam left
阿鸡
Jimmy
有何吩咐， 大哥？
What's the matter, Bro?
B计划
Plan B
B计划是什么？
What's Plan B?
就是A计划少一半， C计划多一半
Half of Plan A plus half of Plan C
那C计划是什么？
What's Plan C?
就是两倍的D计划
Two times of Plan D
再加X计划的八分一
Plus one-eighth of Plan X
和Y计划的十六分一
And one-sixteenth of Plan Y
我数学不太好， 到底要干什么？
Sorry, I'm not good at mathematics What should I do?
给我干掉车房琛 、 黑鬼 、 吹水和牛精
Cancel Sam, Ghost, Lies and Temper
这就明了
I see
干嘛？
What's the matter?
很漂亮
You're so pretty
老婆， 如今关了美容中心
Honey, if I close the beauty salon
你会不会不开心？
Are you upset?
怎么会？更轻松呢
No, I'm much more relaxed
最要紧是你生意好嘛
The most important is your biz's run smoothly
那这些收缩水怎么处理？
How to process the toner?
先摆这里吧， 好吗？
Just leave them here, OK?
我现在出去整头发
I go have my hair cut
等会回来陪你吃饭        好
I'll be back to have dinner with you Great
那我先去洗个澡
I'll take a wash first
你们三个干什么？
What're you doing?
我们已经堕入爱河...
We've fallen in love...
原来你们三个在发情
Are you three on heat?
干活        不行
Go to work Nope
我们约了妞儿去公园亲热
We've dated those gals to the park to smooch
早点说嘛， 玩开心点
Tell me. Enjoy yourself
站住！
Freeze!
想都甭想， 明白吗？
Forget about this, got it?
傻强， 你把外套拿给胖子烫
Crazy Tom, take the coat to Chubbie Chubbie, iron the coat
你给我放水， 我去吃药
You prepare the bath for me I take some pills first
吃什么药？
What pills?
二十四小时充血， 永远保持坚挺
Erect twenty-four hours
金枪巍立不倒， 外表刚劲红润
So powerful
先生口服液！
Viogro!
他到底吃什么药？ 力保健！
What pills does he take? Viagro!
力包颈？
Fiagro?
若我不是警察... 就活活打死他！
If I wasn't a cop... I'd beat him up!
废话， 你是警察， 不能动粗
Bullshit. You're a cop you can't resort to violence
我们就作弄他一次
Then we fool him once
叫他求生不得， 求死不能
And he'll prefer death to live
胖子， 你这样挤， 要挤到明天呀
Chubbie it takes a long time to finish it
这么多 会不会把他缩成一颗猪肉丸？
Will he be a meatball with so much expired toner?
他妨碍我们快活
He curbed our plan
我恨不得把他缩成一粒保济丸呢
I want him to be a meat pill
但是， 我们是卧底
But we're cops
找不到他的犯罪证据 交不了差怎办？
What if we can't collect the evidence of his criminal activities?
犯罪证据？昨天才见他拿了好市民奖
Evidence of his criminal activities? He's rewarded for good citizenship yesterday
狗屁不通
Bullshit
够了， 试试看
It's enough. Have a test first
老婆！
Honey!
老公， 大事不妙
Darling, something goes wrong
什么事？老婆！
What's the matter, honey?
我收到消息， 阿孝要清除异己
I've learnt that Kelvin wanna eliminate the opponents
请杀手来杀四大天王和你呀
He's hired cleaners to kill you and Four Kings
不会吧， 老婆
It shouldn't be the case, darling
我...
I...
干嘛不说话？
Why don't you say something?
我现在... 全身收缩...
My body's minimising...
总之小心点， 你叫阿仁保护你
Be careful. Call Ray
我也不知道他们在哪？
I don't know where the hell they are
我帮你找他们吧
I'll help you to call them
原来他们倒了收缩水！
They put the toner in the bath!
傻强， 你快去车房救琛哥
Crazy Tom, go back to the garage to save Sam
龙永孝派人来杀他呀
Kelvin sends cleaners to kill him
臭小子！
Bastard!
好！我躲到柱子后面， 看你怎么找！
I hide myself at the back of the pillars How can you find me?
行吗？
Does it work?
好厉害
Fabulous
大哥， 洗澡间没人
Bro, nobody in the bathroom
我们去厨房工人房看看
Go to the kitchen and bedroom of the maids
干嘛？
What's the matter?
关灯吓唬那些王八！
Switch the light off and scare those rascals
你这么大声， 那些王八都听见啦
You're too loud and those rascals will hear you
王八？你是说我们？
Bastards? You mean us?
糟！不是这个开关
Shit! Not this switch
王八蛋！
Bastard!
追！
Follow them!
胖子呢？
Where's Chubbie?
见鬼啦你？出来！
What's wrong with you? Come out!
干嘛？想吓唬我？
What do you want? Wanna scare me?
躲起来吓唬他们呀
Hide yourself and scare them
你这样子想吓唬人？
How can you make it with this look?
那怎么样？
How about this?
脱下裤子， 倒立
Take the trousers off and do handstand
这样就能吓倒他们
Then they'll be frightened
大哥， 你怕？
Bro, you fear of the sound?
怕什么？有什么好怕？
Fear the sound? Is it really scaring?
快， 周围搜呀！
Hurry up. Search through!
等等... 这边， 你过来
Wait... this side. Come here
看看那边有什么情况
See what happened on that side
你... 你别慌！别这么慌张！
Don't panic!
只是电话响
Just phone rings
电话你也怕？
You fear the phone?
旺角警署
Police station
昨晚有没有看过VCD呀？
Did you watch the VCD?
有呀， 什么VCD？
Yes. What VCD?
四级， 不打格...
16-rated
一女激战三大汉
Group sex. A woman with three men
连你小舅舅是吗？
And also with your uncle?
那又怎样？
So?
你死定了
You're finished
看完那VCD七小时后
After watching seven-hour VCD
你就会死        少来这套
You'll be dead... Don't play this trick on me
还来午夜凶铃这一招， 行不通啦
Those scaring plots of The Haunting don't work
吓鬼呀？
You scare those ghosts?
鬼就在你后面
The ghost's just behind you
先看看我吧...
Look at me...
真有屁眼鬼呀！
Asshole
晕倒了
He faints
这块是什么？
What's this?
猪肉丸
Meat ball
保济丸
Meat pill
多得你们的收缩水！
Thanks for your toner
嫂子
Mandy
是大嫂
Yes
不， 是丸嫂
It's the wife of meat pill
老公！
Honey!
大嫂...
Hello...
阿仁， 你大哥呢？
Ray, where's your Big Bro?
不知道， 你猜猜
Beats me. Try to guess
你大哥在哪呀？
Where're your Big Bro?
就是刚被你一脚踢出去的墨鱼丸
That octopus ball is Big Bro
老公！
Honey!
那墨鱼丸脏了就别要
If that octopus ball's dirty
不能吃啦！
bin it!
你要我救你的猪兜老公？
Wanna save your stupid husband?
他已经不再是猪兜
He's no longer stupid
他变成一个真正的侏儒
He's a real dwarf
当天他从我手上抢走你之后
When he stole you
知不知道这二十年来...
do you know...
我都生活在失恋的痛苦中
I've been very sad for twenty years?
现在要我去救他， 你真的如此忍心？
You ask me to save him you're so unthoughtful
如果你是爱我的话...
If you love me...
你就帮我救阿琛吧
Please save Sam
为什么？...
Why?
为什么永远都是琛仔赢呢？
Why does Sam always win?
我派阿仁他们去做卧底
I sent Ray, Crazy Tom and Chubbie as undercover
想搜集阿琛的犯罪证据 将他绳之于法
to gather the criminal evidence of Sam
你就会重投我怀抱
Then I'll win you back
没想到阿琛根本没犯罪
Can't believe Sam didn't commit any crime
连随地吐痰都没有
not even spitting
我真的失败！
I lose!
为了你， 我救他
I'll save him for your sake
不用了
No need to do so
车房琛和她都要死
Both Sam and Mandy gotta die
不用怕， 我保护你
Don't panic. I'll protect you
你喜欢吴宇森式...
What style do you like? John Woo or
占士邦式还是李小龙式？
James Bond or Bruce Lee?
吴宇森式我最欣赏
I appreciate John Woo's
好
OK
阿仁， 我和叻长官在天台
Ray, Officer Nat and me are on the rooftop
很多人要杀我们， 你快来呀
There're so many killers. Come quickly
我们快到了， 大嫂， 顶住！
We're coming. Hold on, please
是叻长官约我们来的
It's Officer Nat who made contact with us
没子弹？那你完蛋了
No more bullets? You're finished
没子弹...
No bullets...
你会死得更惨！
You're much more terrible!
这么像李小龙？
Is it like Bruce Lee?
你别死呀
Hold on
你死了， 我们帮你借的赌债怎办？ 王八蛋！
Once you die how can we get the money back, bastard?
快走， 龙永孝的手下追来了
Run. Kelvin's assistants are coming
警察！下车！
Police! Get off!
卡拉OK贵宾卡？
Karaoke VIP card?
好眼力！
Good eyesight!
甭管！下车！
Mind your business! Get off!
我的手表！
My watch!
快走！仁哥！
Run, Ray!
我的劳力士呀...
My Roles...
怎么称呼？
What's your name?
我的劳力士呀！
My Roles!
调头， 取回手表！
Turn back. Take the watch!
撞到什么？
What is it?
大嫂！        糟！
Mandy! Shit!
傻强呢？
Where's Crazy Tom?
刚才撞车， 他被一根铁棒贯穿
He was pricked by a rod during the accident
他有话要跟你说
He got something to tell you
他现在在哪？
Where's he?
他在车里
In the car
傻强！
Crazy Tom!
你来了？
You've come?
快叫救护车！
Call ambulance!
不用了
No
我只想用最后一口气...
It's my last breath. I just want...
跟你说几句真心话
to tell you something from the bottom of my heart
你说吧
Just tell me
以后没有我...
After I go...
你可要小心色狼
be careful of the sex addict
我哪知道谁是色狼？
How can I tell who's the sex addict?
若有一天， 有人伸出舌头跟你谈心事
One day, if someone stretches the tongue to talk to you
但眼睛一直盯着你的胸部...
And he eyes your breasts
那个便是色狼
He's a sex addict
还有呢？
And?
我以前干了很多事...
I've done so many things...
不知道你会不会原谅我？
Will you forgive me?
可你该知道...
You should know...
要是自己喜欢的人不原谅自己
If the one I love doesn't forgive me
那是糟透的事
it's terrible
我会原谅你
I forgive you
我有一点遗憾...
I still have something regrettable...
什么？
What's that?
如果临死前， 都不能跟你亲嘴
If I can't kiss you before I die
那我就死不冥目了
I'll regret forever
你不会死的
No, you won't
舌头都伸出来了
Stretch the tongue out
你看那舌苔， 多难看
Look at the tongue plaque. So horrible
你骗我？
You lie to me?
闹着玩的...
Just for fun...
对了， 狠狠的打
Right, hit him
大圣劈卦？
Is this boxing?
这是傻强的绝招        是吗？
This is Crazy Tom's best card It is?
老婆， 下班
Honey, knock off
下班？不下酒吧吗？
Knock off? Why don't you go to the pub?
是呀， 吃饭了吗？
No, I don't go there. Dinnertime?
差不多了
It's about the dinnertime
我先洗澡
I take a wash first
水龙头在那
Where's the tap?
真棒
Great
小心烫
Beware the hotness
这么烫呀？
Why's it so hot?
真是令人羡慕
What a beautiful picture
就是， 叻长官的外套多漂亮
Yes, Officer Nat's coat is nice
你看大嫂的头... 电得美伦美奂
Look at Mandy's hair style. Amazing
真羡慕他们
What a beautiful picture
也好， 以后三餐不愁
Now they don't worry about their living
天天都这么开心
They're always happy
琛哥， 有什么打算？
What'll you do, Sam?
三个天王都被收买， 我也该走了
Three Kings are assassinated I should go
打算去泰国找个好朋友
Perhaps go to Thailand
投资拍泰国片
to make some Thai films
也好
That's fine
对了， 还有什么没做？
And any other business?
回警署拔针
Remove the undercover in police
我退休了， 你自由了
I retire. You're free
不是吧？
I am?
那我当警察好还是干黑社会好？
Then I should be a cop or a gangster?
你自己决定吧
It's up to you
性无能辅导中心？
lmpotence counseling centre?
打来干嘛？你怎么知道？
Why do you call me? How do you know?
我不是呀！
No!
干吗跟着我？
Why do you follow me?
我是警察
I'm a cop
你不是警察！
You aren't a cop!
你是个性无能的警察！
You're just an impotent cop!
这你也看得出来？
How do you know that?
我不是...
I'm not...
我不是性无能呀！
I'm not impotent!
Angel， 我是阿仁
It's Ray, Angel
我有话跟你说
I got something to tell you
什么事？
What?
我想告诉你我的最大秘密
I wanna tell you my biggest secret
你说吧
Just say it
其实， 我是一个卧底
In fact, I'm an undercover
你笑什么？
Why are you laughing?
阿仁， 现在每天都有一二百人
Ray, there're over a hundred people
说自己是卧底
claiming they're undercover everyday
所以一点都不好笑
So it isn't funny
你有没有打人？
Have you hit anybody?
我没有打人！我是卧底！
No, I haven't! I'm an undercover!
我是梁朝伟！
I'm Tony Leung!
你叫什么名？ 我是梁朝伟！
What's your name? Tony Leung!
你哪地方像梁朝伟？
You look like Tony Leung?
我是卧底！ 你模仿梁朝伟？
I'm an undercover! You imitate him?
有这么多？
So many undercover agents?
大嫂的电话？
Mandy's call?
Sam'sundercover?
Sam's undercover?
没想到这样子找到他！
Can't believe I find him in this way!
你是不是琛哥的卧底？
Are you Sam's undercover?
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
很难查， 但我查到了， 你别装蒜
It's difficult to know that but I make it. Don't act dumb
你是谁？
Who're you?
我是叻长官的卧底
Officer Ye's undercover
我要回复我的身份
I gotta resume my original identity
别动！
Don't move!
一根笔， 就想吓唬我？
Just a sign pen. Anything frightening?
但你穿的是Gucci
But your luxury Gucci...
我划一笔你就惨了
If I draw a line on it. Your Gucci...
千万不要
No
我穿着它出入兰桂坊
This is the only luxury suit
喜宴送殡全靠它
I got to wear it in all special occasions
怕了？
You fear my pen, right?
给我个机会吧
Give me a chance
以前我没得选择
I got no option before
现在我想做个好人
I wanna be a good bloke
对不起， 我是警察
Sorry, I'm a cop
谁知道？
Who knows?
你不知道吗？
Don't you know this?
我知道， 但我已删除你的档案
I know and I've already deleted your file
假聪明， 叶长官也知道
Stupid. Officer Ye also knows
叶长官当然知道
Sure
但自从他结婚后
But after getting married
瞧一眼女人就要顶痰罐
he's always punished just for a glance of women
现在进了精神病医院， 疯了
He's mad He's in psychiatric hospital now
胖子！
Chubbie!
我们全知道了！
We all know!
有没有搞错？
Hey!
胖子， 你这么胖也躲得起来？
How can you hide yourself, Chubbie? You're so fat
阿仁， 我告诉你
Ray, I tell you
我准你跟Angel拍拖
I don't oppose you're in love with Angel
但不可以一起洗澡
But you can't take bath together
谢谢长官！
Thank you. Sir!
我会让她先洗！
Then I let her take a wash first!
华弟， 现在轮到你不是警察
Watson, you aren't a cop now
我是警察！
I'm a cop!
为什么你们不给我机会？ 做什么？
Why don't you give me a chance? What?
这边呀
This side
你投降吧
Lay down your arms
我投你的头！
Lay down your head
是啊！我们帮你求情
Yes, we'll intercede with the judge for you
顶多二十年就能出狱
The expected sentence is around twenty years
就是， 每年八月十五买个月饼给你
True. We'll buy an anniversary cake
补补你的八月十五
to celebrate your anniversary of imprisonment
我不要坐牢！
No. I don't do bird!
别耍花样， 走！
Don't play any tricks. Go
孝哥， 你来得正好
Bro Kelvin, you've come
这次你死定了！
You got no exit!
人到齐了？
Everybody's here?
孝哥， 我是琛哥派到警队里的卧底
Bro Kelvin, I'm Sam's undercover
那些警察都被我摆平了
Those cops're already swayed
我知道
I know
但我今天上来， 是想叫你自首
I come just to tell you to lay down your arms
为什么？
Why?
因为我也想自首
'Cos I also wanna lay down my arms
爸爸死的时候， 我就想自首了
I wanted to lay down my arms when my dad's passed away
我有很多钱， 干嘛还要干黑社会？
I have a lot of money Why do I run gang biz?
但我又怕其他人不同意， 会杀我
But I worried other people would reject my proposal and even kill me
所以硬着头皮上
So I had to go on
你现在不怕他们了？
You don't fear?
其实我们怕他， 他也怕我们
In fact we suspected him, so did he
大家互相猜疑
Both of us suspected the other side
其实我们都想做好人
In fact we all want to be a good bloke
改邪归正嘛
We repent
那你为什么要派人杀琛哥？
Then why did you send killers to kill Sam?
是阿鸡逼我的
It's Jimmy who made me do so
他收我十万块杀人
I gave him a hundred thousand dollars to kill him
却用五百块判给别人干
But he just paid the killer five hundred dollars only
如此廉价， 怎么搞？
How could he make it with such a low price?
昨晚趁他嫖妓时， 我通知警察
When he's patronizing hookers last night
把他抓了
I called the police to cop him
干得好！
Well done!
好...
Well...
你完蛋了
You're finished
不， 大家可以做回本行嘛
No, we work our line of business
你看看那边吧
Look at that side
怎样？是不是自首？
Do you lay down your arms?
那好吧， 大家一起做好人
Then let's be the good blokes
开玩笑， 你刚才这样子也想做好人？
No kidding You really wanna be good bloke?
你准备坐牢吧！
Do bird!
天啊！为什么没人帮我？
Christ! Why isn't there anybody helping me?
冷静点！
Calm down!
别动！我帮你！
Freeze! I help you!
雪柜， 你干什么？
Sharon, what are you doing?
其实当年...
Actually...
我跟他一起被琛哥派去做卧底的
I'm also Sam's undercover
你不记得我啦？
Don't you remember me?
不可能的！
Lmpossible!
当年在庙里， 胸部最大的是我
I had the largest boobs years ago
现在你的胸部比我大得多？
Why are your boobs much larger than mine?
做卧底， 就要卧得彻底
To be undercover you must be cover yourself completely
我是变性人！
I'm a transsexual woman!
你昨晚还跟我亲嘴？
You kissed me last night
对呀， 亲了嘴你还跟我登登登登
You kissed me and then have...
胖子， 什么叫登登登登？
Have what, Chubbie?
是兄弟的你就别问
Don't ask me anymore, OK?
你也想登？
You also want it?
少废话， 把他们都赶进电梯！
No more bullshit Drive them to the lift!
谢谢师兄
Thanks
大家同门兄弟， 不用客气
Welcome. We're from the same line
华弟， 你别这样吧
Watson, don't act in this way
你回头还来得及
You still have the chance
如果你爱我的话...
If you love me...
我没得选择
I get no choice
你有！你自首吧
You do! Lay down your arms
我是说我没得选择才爱上你！
I mean I chose you 'cos I got no choice
你去死吧！
Go to hell!
你进去呀！
Get in
我进去， 缆绳会断的
If I get in, the wire will break
我正想这样
This is what I want
进不进去？不进去就毙了你！
Get in or I shoot you!
原来是你们霸着电梯...
It's you who hold the lift on the twenty-fourth floor
害我爬二十四层楼！
I had to climb the stairs here
大哥！        大哥！
Bro! Bro!
我已经完成任务
I've finished all the jobs
只要这胖子一进电梯
Once this fat bloke gets into the lift
他们就会全部掉下去
they'll all fall down
你就是大哥大了！
You're the biggest Big Bro!
什么大哥大？
What biggest Big Bro?
现在我连自己身份都忘了
I've forgotten my identity
放了他们吧
Release them
那我们是什么？
Who are we?
警察
Cops
我们也忘了刚才发生的事
We forgot what happened too
好啊！
Great!
导演， 你好
Hi, Director
我写这剧本...
I write this script...
是为了纪念跟我一起出生入死
to commemorate those loyal
的卧底同事的一点经历
co-workers
求求你拍了它
Please make this film
卧底故事现在不吃香， 没人看了
But the undercover stories aren't popular
你这样说就不对了
No, it isn't be the case
我这剧本可不一样
This script is different from those undercover stories
连片名都非同凡响
The title is also different
叫做 <无间断卧底之悲欢离合...
It's Infernal Affairs
大狂魔决战弥敦道>
In West End
看， 一听这片名， 你脸都青了
See. What a good title
怎会不行呢？
How can it be a poor film?
这种片名也能卖座， 那就天没眼了
If this is a hit there's no righteousness
扔掉它吧！
Bin it!
无间... 道？
Infernal Affairs?
这片名可以呀， 拍了它
This title is fine. We can make it
你知道故事内容讲什么？
Do you know what the story talks about?
管它， 有梁朝伟和刘德华就行了
Forget about it. It's OK if Tony Leung and Andy Lau are present